Moyyn

Fachkräfte für Deutschland

www.moyyn.com

TECHNOLOGIES/TOOLS

- JavaScript (ES6)
- TypeScript
- React.js
- Redux, Redux-thunk
- CSS/SCSS, HTML, Twig
- work with REST API
- Gatsby.js, headless CMS
- Bootstrap, Material UI
- JQuery, Axios
- NPM. Webpack
- · Git, Github
- RWD-concepts
- BEM-methodology
- SQL/MySQL Server
- Linux/Mac OS X
- Scrum/Agile

PROFILE

I've been learning front-end technologies for over two years. In 2019 I finished the CodersLab (IT-Bootcamp in Warsaw). First practical experience as a Junior Frontend Developer is behind me. Earlier I worked for almost six years for German and Swiss partners in a finance-department.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Miinto Group

12/2019 - 05/2020

Junior Frontend Developer

- Working on the biggest Miinto project SEO
- Frontend of the project (plain JS, Twig, SCSS)
- Administration and SEO panel (Bootstrap, ¡Query)
- Miinterface working on library of components for internal usage (ReactJS)
- Code review and daily reporting (Scrum)

PROJECTS

DAILY MEAL APP

Techn.: **TypeScript**, **ReactJS**, **Redux**, **Material UI**, **ChartJS** Demo: https://lukaszrej.github.io/DailyMealApp

- TypeScript for type-safety
- Redux and Redux-thunk for state management
- Material UI for clean UI,
- Routing, RWD, API communication, DRY

RESUME

Technologies: GatsbyJS, SCSS

Demo: https://lukaszrej.github.io/Resume/

- Website with my current resume
- Clear structure and classes naming, RWD

LOGIN FORM WITH VALIDATION

Technologies: ReactJS, Redux, TypeScript, Material UI https://lukaszrej.github.io/LoginFormWithValidation/

- Login form validated on the frontend level
- Types checked with TypeScript
- Redux for state management

BLOG

Technologies: GatsbyJS, GraphQL, Strapi, SCSS

Demo: https://lukaszrej.github.io/Blog/

- Fetching posts directly from headless CMS (Strapi)
- Clean code/BEM/DRY

TO-DO-LIST

Technologies: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript

Demo: https://lukaszrej.github.io/To-Do-List_JavaScript/

• Responsive to-do-list, plain Vanilla JS (no frameworks)

ADDITIONAL INFO

LANGUAGES

English - very good knowledge (B2) German - very good knowledge (B2) Polish - native

HOBBIES

Drawing, painting Dancing

CALORIE COUNTER

Technologies: ReactJS, SCSS

Demo: https://lukaszrej.github.io/Calorie-Counter_ReactJS/

- API communication, Hash router
- Clean code, DRY

SIT-ON-CHAIR

Fully functional and responsive website Technologies: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript Demo: https://lukaszrej.github.io/SitOnChair/

EDUCATION

CodersLab IT School

10/2018 -06/2019

Field of study: JavaScript Developer: React

Thematic scope: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, SASS, RWD,

jQuery, ECMAScript 6, Git, React JS

University of Lodz

10/2007 – 06/2010 and 10/2010 – 06/2012 Field of study: $\boldsymbol{International\ Relations}$

Specialization: German studies

Degree: Bachelor/Master of International Relations

OTHER WORK EXPERIENCE

Mettler-Toledo International, Inc 01/2019 - 11/2019 SubProcess Leader Dispute Management 01/2018 - 12/2018 Senior AR Accountant 08/2016 - 12/2017 AR Accountant

TRW Automotive (ZF Group)
01/2015 - 04/2016
Junior AR Accountant

PriceWaterhouseCoopers (PwC) 10/2013 - 12/2014 Process Specialist

"I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation)".